flying-hobby.com 2012-10-21

# Privacy Notice : Flying-Hobby.com, Have a nice flying experience everyday!

##   
Information Collection and Use

The privacy of your information is important to us. Our goal is to provide you with a personalized online experience, we appreciate your trust in us handling your information. The customer information obtained are used to facilitate our improvement on your shopping experience at flying-hobby.com. This privacy statement provides detail of the information collected and used. We strongly recommend you to read the statements carefully. Your use of this website constitutes your acceptance of this Privacy Statement.

## 

Non-Personal Information

Non-personal information refers to anonymnous information not directly associated to specific individual. These information may be automatically collect and analyze by flying-hobby.com for evaluation. Non-personal information includes the following: computer and connection information such as the type of browser you use, the server name, operating system, platform and IP address through which you access the internet; the date and time you access the site; purchase history (which we sometimes aggregate with similar information from other customers to create special features, such as Top Sellers and Most Popular); the full URL (Uniform Resource Locator) clickstream to, through and from our Web site; cookie numbers; products you viewed or searched for; and the number of sessions held on our Web site. During some visits, we may use software tools such as JavaScript to measure and gather session information, including page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as clicks, rollovers and scrolling), and methods used to browse away from the page.

##   
Personal Information

Personal information are any information associated with personal identity and permits other parties to contact you. Such as: name, address, telephone/fax number, social security number, credit card number, email address or any information you submitted to us that identifies you individually. It may be collected by flying-hobby.com if you choose to communicate with us through email, via this website, by telephone, in writing, by placing an order, by completing a user registration form or online survey, by creating an address book or using our Shopping Services. It is your choice to provide with such information, but incomplete information may limit the usage in certain features.

##   
Cookies

Cookies are small packets of information websites store in your computer hard drive and may obtain non-personal information to help us target your preferences. It will be stored in your computer's hard drive until you remove it. We also use temporary and session cookies which will expire when you place your order. You can remove, block cookies from your computer's hard drive or receive a warning before they appear on your system. For more information, you can click on your browser's Help button. You may still use our site if you block our cookies, but you limit the operation of certain features, including the shopping cart and checkout areas. Certain business partners may also use cookies on our site, however, we do not accept any responsibility for such use.

## 

Information Sharing with Third Party

flying-hobby.com does not sell, rent, or lease any individual's personal information or lists of email addresses to anyone for marketing purposes, and we take commercially reasonable steps to maintain the security of this information. Should this policy change in the future, we will not do so without your prior consent.

We do not provide personal information to advertisers or third-party websites. Certain third-party website work on their behalf to use technology to send advertisements appearing on our website directly to your browser. This allows them to automatically receive your IP address. They may also use cookies, JavaScript, web beacons (also known as action tags or single-pixel gifs), and other technologies to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. We do not have access to or control over cookies or other features that they may use, and the information practices of these advertisers and third-party websites are not covered by this Privacy Notice. Please contact them directly for more information about their privacy practices. In addition, the Network Advertising Initiative offers useful information about Internet advertising companies (also called "ad networks" or "network advertisers"), including information about how to opt-out of their information collection.

## 

Security

FLYING HOBBY makes every effort to protect personal information of our website users, including using firewalls and other security measures on its servers. Please be aware that no server is 100% secure, and you should take into account when submitting confidential information to any website, including this one. Much personal infromation may be used in conjunction with participation-level service such as discussions, certain personal information may be exposed to other FLYING HOBBY participants and to the public. FLYING HOBBY assumes no liability for the interception, alteration or misuse of the information you provide.

## 

Contact Information

If you have any question or suggestion regarding our privacy policy, please contact our Customer Service at: cs@flying-hobby.com
